{
    "subject": "resource/Maxime_Chaya",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Maxime Chaya was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9191485047340393,
            "question": "Is Maxime Chaya from Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8555006980895996,
            "question": "Where was Maxime Chaya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6171059608459473,
            "question": "What nationality is Maxime Chaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941148400306702,
            "question": "What country is associated with Maxime Chaya's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4217713177204132,
            "question": "What is Maxime Chaya known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3947494924068451,
            "question": "Where might Maxime Chaya have grown up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3717099726200104,
            "question": "What are some potential interests of someone born in Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32310009002685547,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Maxime Chaya's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2723267376422882,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Maxime Chaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21391978859901428,
            "question": "Has Maxime Chaya made any significant contributions to society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maxime Chaya was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_506_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Maxime Chaya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_506_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Maxime Chaya's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_506_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential interests of someone born in Lebanon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_506_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_506_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can determine that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention Maxime Chaya's birthplace as Beirut, which is a city located in Lebanon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Maxime Edgard Chaya was born and raised in Beirut, Lebanon. Therefore, the triple \"Maxime Chaya was born in Lebanon\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}